What I'm doing here is I'm just kind of finishing up shaping my little orchid here.
What I'm going to do is take these leaves and I think I'm going to fold them over one more time down here.
Just a little bit more.
Then I'm going to take them in my chopstick just really put a real good twist on them.
Cause when you see the plant they have the leaves here and they twist as with age.
They just kind of twist and hang down and you can just manually grab it and twist it by hand if you want to.
Just what ever it takes to give it the plant look that it really deserves.
Give it a little bit here, a little more here, a little fold here.
Just grab it and just twist it all along up here.
Just work with it a little bit and this how your golden slipper plant should look of course I'm going to work with it a little bit more to get it to looking right but essentially this is how you do it.